(engines revving)
(horn honking)
(chill music)
-Hey, Wow! Look at this car!
- Look at this car.
Hey, this is a--
- It's a DeLorean.
- Hey, guys.
- Where's that $5 you owe me?
- [Man] Okay, Huey, I think
we're all set for ya.
[Huey] Really, oh.
Okay, this is it.
We're back, we're back.
(crowd applauding)
I told you we'd be back, right?
- Wow, look at the stereo.
- No, no, no,
don't touch that,
it's not a stereo.
- What is it?
- It's what it is.
- Now I know, I know
it's been a few years.
I know it's been a few years
but Hollywood finally called.
(crowd cheering)
That's it, your favorite group
is in the movie business.
(crowd cheering)
(engine rumbling)
- What's going on in there?
- Music.
- What kind of music?
- Dancing, rock & roll.
- Huey.
- Hu Huey?! This is the place!
I've gotta get in there.
They're expecting me.
- Come on, let's go.
- Keep an eye on my machine.
Don't touch anything.
I'll be right back.
- I know it's a good song.
And I mean, it's
gotta be a good movie,
they even got jackets.
Gonzo, show 'em your jacket.
(crowd cheering)
Check this out.
For real.
(machine beeping)
(engine revving)
Here it is, the moment
you've been waiting for,
From the big smash-hit movie.
(crowd cheering)
Our latest single,
The Power of Love.
(crowd cheering)
(engine revving)
(air whooshing)
(upbeat music)
♪ The power of love
is a curious thing ♪
♪ Make a one man weep,
make another man sing ♪
♪ Change a hawk to a
little white dove ♪
♪ More than a feeling,
that's the power of love ♪
♪ Tougher than diamonds,
rich like cream ♪
♪ Stronger and harder
than a bad girl's dream ♪
♪ Make a bad one good,
mm make a wrong right ♪
♪ Power of love will
keep you home at night ♪
♪ Don't need money,
don't take fame ♪
♪ Don't need no credit
card to ride this train ♪
♪ It's strong and it's sudden
and it's cruel sometimes ♪
♪ But it might just
save your life ♪
♪ That's the power of love ♪
♪ First time you feel
it might make you sad ♪
♪ Next time you feel
it might make you mad ♪
♪ But you'll be glad
baby when you're found ♪
♪ That's the power that
makes the world go 'round ♪
♪ And it don't take
money, don't take fame ♪
♪ Don't need no credit
card to ride this train ♪
♪ It's strong and it's sudden,
it can be cruel sometimes ♪
♪ But it might just
save your life ♪
♪ They say that all
in love is fair ♪
♪ Yeah but you don't care ♪
♪ But you know what to do ♪
♪ When it gets hold of you ♪
♪ And with a little
help from above ♪
♪ You feel the power of love ♪
(Croud applauding)
♪ Can you feel it ♪
♪♪♪
(crowd applauding)
♪ It don't take money,
don't take fame ♪
♪ Don't need no credit
card to ride this train ♪
♪ Tougher than diamonds
and stronger than steel ♪
♪ You won't feel
nothin' 'til you feel ♪
♪ You feel the power,
feel the power of love ♪
♪ That's the power,
that's the power of love ♪
♪ You feel the power of love ♪
♪ Feel the power of love ♪
(crowd cheering)
- [Woman] Thanks, Doc,
what a great trip.